

Philip Loki Hybertz Haugaard

I am a specialist in being a generalist. If I don't know it, I'll learn it.

✓ loki@theLuckyLoki.dk · • Copenhagen · in Philip haugaard Loves to code so much, I even coded this resume!

Skills
Learning - Skilled - Expert
C# / -Net / .Net Core
Unity
Mobile Development
Web Development
Backend Experience
Frontend Experience
Cloud Experience
Agile & Scrum
Git
Languages
English
Danish

Profile

I am a highly dedicated and engaged developer, with a love for designing and developing solutions. As a developer I prefer to work in flat-structured teams, and I dedicate myself to delivering honest, high quality and most importantly realistic results.

With over 10 years of experience, I have developed a flexible skill-set which means I am very comfortable as a Fullstack developer; and while I prefer working in a team setting, I am also comfortable working solo.

I am looking for a place where quality, code reviews, pair-coding and automated testing aren't just words, but a respected and cared for discipline.

Experience

Fullstack Developer

nov 2024 - Current

ITM8 - Custom Software

Working in the Custom Software department as a fullstack developer / consultant. I am primarily working in .Net azure, yet my day to day take me everywhere from coding to setting up CI/CD workflows, project management, docker, DevOps responsibilities, client communications, and much more.

Tech & Team Lead /Sr. Fullstack Developer

Oct 2023 - Oct 2024

Fysiofresh

Hired to help design & develop a digital platform for fysiotherapy.

Using vueJS, vuetify, PostgreSQL, Vitest, PGTap, Playwright, Docker and more.

I assembled and mentored an agile team that provided steady value through TDD.

Tech & Team Lead /Sr. Game Developer

Sep 2022 - July 2023

SweatyPalms

Hired in a newly formed Hyper Casual Studio, my role was to organize the day-to-day of our developers; help develop games, as well as assist & teach junior developers.

Sr. Game Developer

June 2021 - June 2022

Riddlehouse

Hired as Tech Lead for a team developing an application for doing historical street-treasure hunts. During my employment, I worked with DotNetCore, Unity, NUnit, MoQ, Kubernetes and GO. (C#) for Android and iOS development.

Fullstack Engineer

July 2019 - May 2021

UptimeDevelopment

Hired as a remote developer, developing various solutions, P.O.Cs, M.V.Ps, and all-round consultancy work.

Cloud Software Engineer

Feb 2019 - June 2019

Cloudeon

Hired into the Cloudeon Digital Garage, to work as the first contact between sales and development.

Lead Developer, Project Manager, CTO (Fullstack)

Oct 2017 - Jan 2019

App-Works

Part of a 4-clover partnership, to consult, design & develop customer-centric-solutions. In this role I worked between Sales, Client and Development teams; working directly with the customers to achieve their dreams.

Game Developer April 2017 - Oct 2017

Pointvoucher

Hired as the first in-house unity developer – during my time at Pointvoucher I designed and developed the foundations for their future backend connection plugin, and developed several frontend pieces of their apps "Playlondon w. mr. Bean" & "Tal Ordentligt." Furthermore I helped maintain the existing apps – "Far til Fjorten Bilka" and "Tivoli Puzzle."

Freelance Game Developer (\emptyset)

Jan 2017 - April 2017

Built a prototype for an island simulator game in unity.

Software developer (SPIIO)

Aug 2016 - Dec 2016

Developed website adaptations and API branches for their online platform in their early startup days.

Software Developer (*it-works.dk*)

Aug 2015 - June 2016

Worked in a variety of app development and web development system over the course of a year.

Education

BSc in Medialogy

2012 - 2015

Aalborg University

Aalborg University Copenhagen. Focused on a broad wing of concepts, ranging from graphics design & 2D/3D animation all the way into micro-electronics & procedural programming. Medialogy was an incredible foundation for an extremely flexible skillset that I enjoy to this day.

HTX

2009 - 2012

CPH WEST

Aalborg University Copenhagen. Major in Communications and IT, with focus on design and development.

Honorable Mentions

AB-Ringaarden

2020 - current

Sr. Boardmember

After purchasing a condo in Glostrup, I quickly joined the board, and am now helping to facilitate everything from cleaning, renovations, complaints, and more. General facility management stuff, and what you might expect to be needed in a smaller apartment building of 48 apartments

Bread'It 2023

Nordic Game Jam

Working with the LEGO TechniQ parts, Unity and a communication bridge supplied by the LEGO team - we built a 'bobbit' inspired gizmo for children to play with. We tested the physical device on other NGJ participants, and children with great success. The Bread'it won an unofficial LEGO award for the 'craziest contraption'

Extended Leadership Course (10)

2021

Taught by Martin Nørtoft

As I started at Riddlehouse, I was hired as the team lead for the tech team. I was given roughly 30 hours of education in Management vs. Leadership, the history of, practical application, understanding and adapting leadership styles, coaching and mentoring, as well as the legalese - do's and don'ts as a leader as well as hiring/firing, within the danish legal landscape.

Founding partner of App-Works

2017-2020

Independent

Worked as an independent consultant with my 3 partners for 3 years, paying my own wages, developing my own and customer projects.

Champster 2016-2019

Partnered with Magnus Elvstrøm Myrälf

A private racing game project about hamsters in terrarium tubes. Developed for PC, and Mobile Platforms; with and without controller support. <u>Early prototype video.</u>

Flux 2019

Interactive art installation at the Danish Museum for women.

Helping out with the application development of a museum piece. Was exhibited for several months at the Danish museum for women.

Finalist 2017

Nordic Game Jam

Honored as a finalist with my team and game GeoNigma at NGJ2017.

Lieutenant 2016

Nordic Game Jam

Worked as a lieutenant for the event coordinators, to help organize other volunteers.

Volunteer 2015

Nordic Game Jam

Worked as a volunteer during the event.